

ALI HAMEDELNEEL

Mobile Application Developer









Github:https://github.com/alialdwahy

ABOUT ME

Having over 3+ years of IT experience in Software Development Life -Cycle (SDLC) preparing Requirement.

Developing the Front-end infrastructure using Dart, Flutter

Framework . and Developing Back-End using JavaScript ,Node js and PHP Laravel .

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- · Git&GitHub
- REST Api
- Flutter
- · Node is
- Laravel
- .Net Core
- · Microsoft Office
- SQL Server
- MongoDB
- MySQL

CERTIFICATIONS

Git&Github Udemy

Learn Flutter and Dart to Create Android and IOS Apps Udemy

Full Stack Mobile Application Development Udemy

Flutter with Firebase&Stripe Build shop app Udemy

Flutter&Dart the Complete Guide Udemy

programming Foundations Fundamentals LinkedIn

Complete Node js E-Commerce Udemy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Expert Company
Ministry of Culture(KSA)

Flutter Developer Apr 2022 to Present

Najah Dot Com

Full stack Mobile Developer (Per Project)

Jan 2022 to Apr 2022

Oasis Computer system Full Stack Mobile Developer July 2021 to Feb 2022

Zite Software

Software Engineer Jan 2020 to Mar 2021

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Dart
- Java Script
- Php
- Java
- C#
- JavaFX

SKILLS

- Complex Problem Solver
- Work Very Will in a Team
- Ability to Find Creative solutions
- · Strong Decision Maker
- Great Communication Skills

EDUCATIONAL

2017-2021

Bachelor Degree Honors in Information Technology UNIVARSTY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Al-Mamoon Mobile Application(Salesmen) - KSA, Al Mamoon Insurance Brokers

Building an Insurance Broker application using Fultter by using GetX Framework also Includes UI design and Mobile Integration and Backend using .Net core Framework .

using Version Control System [Git] and Team Foundation Manage the Tasks.

Oasis Computer System

Al Mamoon Mobile Application (Clients) - KSA, Al Mamoon Insurance Brokers

Objective: Development of a fully integrated mobile application for the company's clients to help them keep track and submit their policies, requests, complaints, claims, and view statements of accounts.

Contributions:

Gather and analyze requirements. Involved in all stages of software development life cycle. Creating and maintaining the server-side application using .Net Core Restful API. Collbatore with front-end developers on combining their front-end elements and components with the Restful API. Optimize the Restful API for high performance, high availability, and low latency. Work on security and data protection.

Oasis Computer System

Al Mamoon Mobile Application (HR Panel) - KSA, Al Mamoon Insurance Brokers Objective: Development of a fully integrated mobile application for the company's clients to help them keep track and submit their policies, requests, complaints, claims, and view statements of accounts.

Contributions:

Gather and analyze requirements. Involved in all stages of software development life cycle. Creating and maintaining the server-side application using .Net Core Restful API. Collbatore with front-end developers on combining their front-end elements and components with the Restful API. Optimize the Restful API for high performance, high availability, and low latency. Work on security and data protection.

Oasis Computer System

Shadid Mobile Application

Building an Insurance Broker application using Fultter by using GetX Framework also Includes UI design and Mobile Integration and Backend using .Net core Framework.

using Version Control System [Git] and Team Foundation Manage the Tasks.

Oasis Computer System

E-Commerce Application

Building an Shopping Application and Web Backend Application Api using Node js Framework . Freelancer in Mustagil

Belhalal Mobile Application

Building an Belhalal application Api using Node js Framework and Mobile Integration using Flutter Framework. using Version Control System [Git} Najah Dot Com

ERP Mobile Application

building an ERP mobile Application in Ministry of Culture(KSA) using Flutter Framework and GetX Framework also Integration with Odoo System, work with Cyber Security Team and Quality Tame.